

A ygaojiany.github.io

ygaojiany@gmail.com

(+86) 18255627780

github.com/yGaoJiany

Suzhou, China

Google Scholar

ABOUT

I am a 1st-year Ph.D. student at the School of Intelligent Science and Technology at Nanjing University, under the mentorship of Professors Yao Yao and Tieniu Tan. My research primarily centers on 3D reconstruction and differentiable rendering.

Prior to this, I earned my M.S. and B.S degrees from Wuhan University mentored by Prof. Shunping Ji. During my master's program, I focused on the study of multi-view stereo techniques.

EDUCATION

Sept. 2024 –	Ph.D. Computer Science and Technology	Nanjing University
	School of Intelligent Science and Technology	
Sept. 2020 – June 2023	M.S. Pattern Recognition and Intelligent Systems	Wuhan University
	School of Remote Sensing and Information Engineering	
Sept. 2016 – June 2020	B.S. Science and Technology of Remote Sensing	Wuhan University
	School of Remote Sensing and Information Engineering	
	GPA : 3.86 / 4.0	

PUBLICATIONS

* Equally contributed.

- [1] Shuang Li*, Yibing Wang*, Jian Gao*, Chulhong Kim, Seongwook Choi, Yu Zhang, Qian Chen, Yao Yao, Changhui Li. Sliding Gaussian Ball Adaptive Growth: Point Cloud-based Iterative Algorithm for Large-scale 3D Photoacoustic Imaging. ArXiv, 2024.
- [2] Jian Gao*, Chun Gu*, Youtian Lin, Zhihao Li, Hao Zhu, Xun Cao, Li Zhang, and Yao Yao. Relightable 3D Gaussians: Realistic Point Cloud Relighting with BRDF Decomposition and Ray Tracing. ECCV, 2024.
- [3] Jin Liu, Jian Gao, Shunping Ji, Chang Zeng, Shaoyi Zhang, and Jian Ya Gong. Deep learning based multi-view stereo matching and 3D scene reconstruction from oblique aerial images. ISPRS, 2023.
- [4] Jian Gao, Jin Liu, and Shunping Ji. A general deep learning based framework for 3D reconstruction from multiview stereo satellite images. ISPRS, 2023.
- [5] Jian Gao*, Jin Liu*, and Shunping Ji. Rational polynomial camera model warping for deep learning based satellite multi-view stereo matching. ICCV, 2021.

EXPERIENCES

Research Assistant

Sept. 2023 - Sept. 2024

School of Intelligence Science and Technology, Nanjing University under the supervision of Prof. Yao Yao.

Teaching Assistant

Feb. 2020 - July. 2020 & Feb. 2021 - July. 2021

School of Remote Sensing and Information Engineering, Wuhan University

Course: Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition

AWARDS AND HONORS

Outstanding Graduates	May 23th, 2023
First Class Entrance Scholarship for New Students	Sept. 10th, 2020
Outstanding Graduates	May 4th, 2020
Wang Zhizhuo innovative talent scholarship [Only 4 undergrads university-wide annually awarded]	Dec. 20th, 2019